toolking.com 2012-10-22

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**NOTE FOR FESTOOL CUSTOMERS:** As a Festool dealer, it is a requirement per Festool that Tool King register tools on the behalf of our Festool customers. As a result your name, company name, address, phone number & email address will be shared with Festool.

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

This site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors on this site, and understanding how visitors use our Site. Cookies can also help customize our site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate (non-personal) cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, DinosaurBedding.net has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### Google Trusted Stores

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve the badge on your website and to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.)

### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. We will NOT share your personal information with other companies or agencies for marketing purposes.

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

### Passwords

While creating an account with Tool King, you will be asked to provide a personal password. This password will be used for all future access to your account. The password should be something the user will easily remember. You will be provided with a Password Hint drop-down. This box will allow you to pick a word that relates to something like your hometown or your pets name. You will also be able to give yourself a hint, to ensure you remember. If you do happen to forget your password or login your password incorrectly, simply click on the 'Forgot Password' link under the member login area. We will email you the password. (For security reasons, we cannot assign a password for you, nor can we provide it to you over the phone in case you forget it.  

### SSL Technology

Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is presently the safest way to send credit card information over the Internet. Information is first encrypted on your computer, then decrypted on our server, preventing anyone from accessing any information in between. To ensure your security, we recommend the use of SSL-capable browsers, like Netscape 3.0 or Internet Explorer 3.0 or higher.

### Clicktale Tracking

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as text you type in this website. This site does not use ClickTale to collect any personally identifiable information entered in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see [Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx). We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to improve our website. You can choose to disable the Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

  * By E-Mail: [TKHelpDesk@toolking.com](http://toolking.com/contacts "Contact ToolKing.com Customer Support")
  * By Phone: 1-800-696-8665  Monday-Friday  8:00 AM - 5:00 PM (MST) 

_**We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.**_
